今天真棒 谢谢你们
What a wonderful day, thank you.
你开心 我们就开心
Oh, we're glad you had fun.
一杯蓝色沙冰 外加去一次"收纳箱"专卖店?
Blue Icees and a trip to The Container Store?
就好像到了死了之后被推到解剖室
It's like I died and went to the post-mortem,
神经元造成的幻觉让人误以为是天堂的地方
neuron-induced hallucination commonly mistaken as heaven.
我还是不明白你为什么要买药盒
I still don't understand why you bought that pill caddie.
你还年轻
You're a young man.
年龄是一种心态 Leonard
Age is a state of mind, Leonard.
我心理上已经90岁了
In here I'm 90.
你为什么要把收纳箱拿到那边去?
Why are you taking your bins over there?
我就想放在这里呢
That's just where I need them.
要知道 她的衣柜空间不大
You know, she doesn't have a lot of closet space.
你自己的衣柜怎么了?
What's wrong with your closet?
呃...
Uh...
亲爱的 你得明白
Well, honey, you know,
现在我和Leonard结婚了
now that Leonard and I are married,
照理说就应该住在一起
it kind of makes sense that we actually live together.
所以今天就为了这个?
So that's all this day was?
在告诉我坏消息前安抚好我?
A plan to butter me up before delivering bad news?
- 别这样 兄弟  - 我还以为我们是朋友呢
- Come on, buddy.  - No, I thought we were friends.
你还想喝一口我的沙冰呢
You asked for a sip of my Icee.
如果你有自己的吸管 我也许就会同意了
If you had your own straw, I might've said yes.
Sheldon 别这样 我们已经感觉够糟了
Sheldon, please, we already feel bad about this.
你知道"收纳箱"店里不卖什么吗?
You know what they don't sell at The Container Store?
就是大到能装下我此刻失望的收纳箱
Something large enough to contain my disappointment.
虽说
Although,
有店会卖的话 也就他们那家店了
if anyone did, it would be them.
* 宇宙一度又烫又稠密 *
* Our whole universe was in a hot, dense state *
* 140亿年前终于爆了炸... 等着瞧! *
* Then nearly 14 billion years ago expansion started... Wait! *
* 地球开始降温 *
* The Earth began to cool *
* 自养生物来起哄 穴居人发明工具 *
* The autotrophs began to drool, Neanderthals developed tools *
* 我们建长城 我们建金字塔 *
* We built the Wall We built the pyramids *
* 数学 自然科学 历史 揭开神秘 *
* Math, Science, History, unraveling the mystery *
* 一切由大爆炸开始 *
* That all started with a big bang *
生活大爆炸 第九季第4集
--==圣城家园SCG字幕组 http://hdscg.com/==--
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
协调: 还在狂写作业的凤梨酥
时间轴: 奥利奥   校对: UUUUUU
翻译: 水煮影 小黄不小黄 波特妹子 哈利波特 凤梨酥 猫呗
谢谢你允许我来和你聊聊
Thank you for letting me come speak with you.
不客气
Of course.
鉴于我和Penny以及Amy的关系
As my relationships with Penny and Amy
最近闹僵了 我得来找你
are currently strained, I'm turning to you
寻求女性的宽慰和鼓励
for female comfort and encouragement.
- 真荣幸  - 我试过
- I'm honored.  - I tried
联系我妈妈 但她在研究圣经
reaching out to my mother, but she was in Bible study.
Leonard的妈妈在开签售会
Leonard's mother is on a book tour.
我奶奶在午睡
My Mee-Maw was taking a nap,
我吐槽了一会儿 连Siri都开始给重复答案了
and after a while Siri started repeating her answers.
所以我是第七个人选
So, I'm your seventh choice.
对 跻身前十 很开心吧
Yeah, I know, top ten, pretty exciting.
我能怎么帮你?
How can I help you?
现在不仅Amy离开了我
Well, in addition to Amy leaving me,
Leonard也要搬去和Penny住了
Leonard's moving in with Penny.
很难不觉得自己被抛弃了
It's difficult not to feel abandoned.
你为什么不把这事当成是一次机遇?
Well, why don't you look at this as an opportunity?
在Leonard之前 你也有过其他室友
You had other roommates before Leonard.
也许是时候
Maybe this is a chance
找个新欢了
to find someone new.
也许我该找个比Leonard更棒的
Perhaps I could find someone better than Leonard.
给他点颜色看看
Someone I can rub in his face.
克里斯·帕拉特现在就很吃香
Chris Pratt's all the rage right now.
主演"银河守卫队"及"侏罗纪世界"的男演员
不知道他乐意
I wonder how he'd feel
去住那个副卧不
about taking the smaller bedroom.
- 嘿  - 嘿
- Hey.  - Hey.
你知道谁是完美室友吗?
You know who would be the perfect roommate?
甘道夫 但他会抽烟
Gandalf, but he's a smoker.
"魔戒"人物
是Stuart
Stuart.
他已经和我们同住了一段时间
He's been living with us for a while now.
我想他应该会很乐意脱离我们的魔爪
I'm sure he'd love to get us out of his hair.
不乐意 我住得很开心
Nope, couldn't be happier.
Sheldon正在找...
Well, Sheldon's looking for a...
不要
Nope.
- 他会考虑的  - 我不会!
- He'll think about it.  - No I won't!
你看了这部阿奇漫画吗?
Have you seen this Archie comic?
竟然是说阿奇对战掠食者的
It's actually Archie versus Predator.
阿奇怎么可能打败掠食者?
How could Archie defeat Predator?
我不知道
I don't know.
也许琼斯是个终结者
Maybe Jughead's a Terminator.
- 嘿  - 嘿 Stuart
- Hey.  - Hey, Stuart.
你们认识什么音乐家吗?
Do you guys know any musicians?
干嘛问这个?
Why?
我在想一周选几天
I was thinking it might be cool
晚上请人来现场演奏
to have live music here a few nights a week.
就是让这家店多些
You know, give this place more
"还没倒闭"的气氛
of a "Staying in business" vibe.
你想要什么类型的音乐?
What kind of music are you thinking of?
我喜欢各种类型的音乐 但我最喜欢的是免费音乐
I like all kinds of music, but my favorite genre is free.
嘿 我们一直说
Hey, we've always talked
要一起演奏的
about playing together.
玩玩弹唱
Well, it could be fun
也挺不错的
to try a little acoustic thing.
我们可以表演"科谣"音乐
Oh, we could play "Filk" music.
那是什么?
What's that?
这种音乐已经流行好几年了
It's been around for years.
和民谣很像 但是以科幻为主题
It's like folk music, but with a sci-fi/fantasy theme.
我喜欢
I like it.
听上去这东西我肯定
It sounds exactly like something
不需要花钱请人来表演
I shouldn't be expected to pay for.
哥们 首先
Dude, if we do this,
我们得想一个帅气的乐队名称出来
we're gonna need a cool band name.
其实我很多年前
You know, I've actually
已经想好一个名字了
had one I've been sitting on for years.
真的吗?
Really?
我初中的时候想组一个
It was for this power trio
三人的摇滚乐队
I tried to put together in junior high,
但是我还差两个朋友
but I was short two friends.
叫什么?
What is it?
月球上的脚印
Footprints on the Moon.
我都起鸡皮疙瘩了
I just got chills.
我也是
So did I.
Me, too.
不过我... 我有可能得了莱姆病
But I... I might have Lyme Disease.
你再签几个名就好了
Just a few more signatures, and we'll be finished.
这里签名 确认你已经归还钥匙了
Initial here to acknowledge that you've returned your key.
好的
Okay.
你马上就是我的邻居了
As my future neighbor,
我把家门钥匙给你
I'd like you to have a key.
这里签名确认你已经拿到了我的钥匙
Initial here to acknowledge you received it.
我真为你自豪 你处理的非常好
I'm proud of you. You're taking this really well.
又不是我再也见不到你们了
Well, it's not like I'm never going to see you two again.
看到这里 23号文件C段...
Which brings us to article 23 subsection C...
在这里签名
please check here to reserve your spot
预留十年室友团聚会的门票
at the ten year roommate reunion.
我一定得现在签名吗?
Do I really have to do that now?
不一定 不过要是你到时候想吃鸡
No, but if you want chicken
结果只剩下鱼了 那就别怪我
and get stuck with the fish, that's on you.
好的
All right.
最后
Oh, and lastly,
在这里签名确认
please initial here to confirm
客厅里的沙发所有权
that ownership of the living room couch
从此在全宇宙的一切时空下
is hereby transferred to me
和所有的平行宇宙中
in perpetuity all throughout the universe
转让给我
and all alternate universes
除了那些蜂王禁止人们
except for those universes where owning a couch
拥有沙发的平行宇宙
is forbidden by the hive queen.
蜂王万岁
In which case, all glory to the hive queen.
好了 最后
All right, now all that's left
我们需要在这个文件上签上姓名和日期
is for us to sign and date the document,
从此我们就正式解除室友关系
and we will officially no longer be roommates.
怎么了?
What's the matter?
这比我想象中的难
It's harder than I thought.
我来帮你
Let me help you.
这么拼L-e-o-n...
L-e-o-n...
这有帮助
That helped.
我有一首科谣歌曲的灵感
So I have an idea for a filk song.
有点像是
Kind of a,
一种力量民谣 史诗角度来写的
a power ballad, superhero crossover tale
超级英雄对战
of epic proportions.
这里冷吗
Is it cold in here,
天啊
'cause, oh, my.
这是个以弱胜强的故事
Okay, so it's a, it's a David and Goliath story.
讲的是凡人面对神
It's about man against God.
歌名叫"锤子和鞭子:
It's called "Hammer and Whip:
"索尔和印第安纳·琼斯
"The Untold Story
不为人知的故事"
of Thor versus Indiana Jones."
索尔和印第安纳·琼斯?
Thor versus Indiana Jones?
你让我大"科"眼界了
You just blew my filking mind.
我还没全部写完
Okay, I don't have it all worked out yet,
我现在只有个大概...
but I was thinking something like, um...
# 哦 印第 #
# Oh, Indy #
# 天空风起 #
# The skies are so windy #
# 那人在飞 像杀手一样 #
# Is that a flying man with a killer bod #
# 等等 #
# Wait #
# 那不是人 #
# That's no man #
# 那是挪威的神 #
# It's a Norse god. #
太好了
Oh yes, definitely.
等等
Hang on.
# 索尔举起了锤 电闪雷鸣 #
# Thunder clapped as Thor raised his mighty hammer #
# 印第唱到 真狂霸酷拽叼 #
# Indy rapped, "That's one bad mamma-jamma." #
这... 太好了!
That... that is so good!
对吧?
Right?
我就这么想到了
Mamma-jamma just came to me.
接下来是副歌
Okay, and here's the hook.
# 索尔和琼斯博士 #
# Thor and Dr. Jones #
# 一个玩闪电 #
# One plays with lightning #
# 一个玩骨头 #
# The other plays with bones #
# 索尔和琼斯博士 #
# Thor and Dr. Jones #
# 一个玩闪电 #
# One plays with lightning #
# 另一个玩骨头 #
# The other plays with bones #
天啊 太好听了
Oh, man. That rocks.
嘿 还记得消失的约柜(圣经故事)吗?
Hey, remember The Ark of the Covenant?
- 怎么了?  - 凡听我们表演者皆会把膝盖献上
- Yeah?  - That's how much we're gonna melt people's faces off.
很感谢你对公寓有兴趣
I appreciate your interest in the apartment.
我只需要问你几个常规问题
I just need to ask you a few standard questions.
- 好的  - 表上说你是个化学家
- Sure.  - It says here you're a chemist.
你觉得元素周期表里
Which element on the periodic table
哪个元素的裤子太小了?
do you feel is too big for its britches?
你是在讲笑话吗?
Is that supposed to be a joke?
看来氩(惰性气体)不是唯一一个
Looks like argon's not the only one
态度有问题的
with an attitude problem.
通常来说
In general,
你是比现在好闻些 难闻些
would you say that you smell better, worse
还是差不多呢?
or the same as you do right now?
我本想问你
I was going to ask you
最好的水果是什么
what is the best fruit,
但后来意识到我想问你的是
but then I realized what I want to ask you
为什么你的前臂上有创可贴
is why is there a Band-Aid on your forearm,
但再后来发现
but then I realized what
我真的想跟你说的是
I really want to ask you is
你能走吗?
just can you just go?
你很健康
You're healthy.
你在科学界工作
You have a job in the sciences.
我不得不说 如果信用报告反馈好的话
I've got to say, if this credit report comes back good,
你是优先候选人
you're the frontrunner.
我不会当你室友的 Sheldon
I'm not gonna be your roommate, Sheldon.
但我已经见了十一个人了
But I met with 11 people,
他们都不行
and they all walked out.
而那个势利眼Chris Pratt
And that Hollywood phony Chris Pratt
推特上没理我
never tweeted me back.
你肯定能找到别人的
I'm sure you'll find somebody else.
但愿吧
I suppose.
我这是怎么了 Amy?
What happened to me, Amy?
几年前
Years ago I was
我跟自己的感情是完全脱离的
completely disengaged from my feelings.
我想说那个时候更开心
I'd say it was a happier time,
但我跟感情脱离了 谁知道呢?
but I was disengaged from my feelings, so who can tell?
我不知道该怎么帮你
I don't know how to help you.
感情是生活的一部分
You know, feelings are a part of life.
以前不是
They didn't used to be.
你和Leonard和Penny
You and Leonard and Penny,
你们用感情荼毒了我
you all poisoned me with emotions.
(出自绿野仙踪)
我就像铁皮人 在恶巫师给他心之前
I was like the Tin Man, perfectly content
无忧无虑地生活着
until that evil Wizard gave him a heart.
电影的主题不是这个吧
I don't think that was the point of the movie.
好吧 那我就是被怪人杰佩托(老木工)
Fine, then I was like Pinocchio
变成真正的男孩之前的匹诺曹
before that jerk Geppetto went and made him a real boy.
这才对嘛
There you go.
你晚饭想吃什么?
So, what are you thinking for dinner?
今晚是泰国菜之夜
Well, it's Thai food night.
亲爱的
Well, honey,
你不再跟着Sheldon住了
you don't live with Sheldon anymore.
你想吃什么都可以
You can have anything you want.
你说得对
You're right.
但吃什么呢?
But what?
墨西哥菜?
Mexican?
意大利菜? 德国菜?
Italian? German?
印度菜? 希腊菜?
Indian? Greek?
古巴菜? 中餐?
Cuban? Chinese?
披萨? 烧烤?
Pizza? Barbecue?
韩国菜? 韩国烧烤?
Korean? Korean barbecue?
吃泰国菜怎么样?
How about Thai food?
谢天谢地
Oh, thank God
嘿 我们要去吃晚饭 你要来吗?
Hey, we're going to dinner. You want to come?
哦 我很想去
Oh, I wish I could,
但我意识到我变得情绪太脆弱了
but I realized I've become too emotionally vulnerable,
所以 就像操作系统一样
so, like an operating system,
我要把生活恢复到最近一个稳定的版本
I'm restoring my life to the last stable version,
也就是2003年 我见到Leonard的前一天
which was in 2003, the day before I met Leonard.
你听见了 他不去
You heard him, no.
等下
Hang on.
慢着 你真的以为现在2003年?
Wait, you actually think it's 2003?
不 虽然我要过跟十二年前一样的生活
No, just because I'm living my life
但我并没有精神失常
like it was 12 years ago doesn't mean I'm delusional.
而既然现在是2003年
And since it is 2003,
我不认识你
I don't know who you are,
所以请在我用最新款翻盖手机报警前
so please exit the premises
离开这里
before I call the police on my stylish new flip phone.
你还好吧?
Are you doing okay?
应该吧
I guess.
我只是担心Sheldon
I'm just, you know, worried about Sheldon.
别这样 他是个在假装自己二十岁的
Well, come on, he's a grown man in his 30s
三十岁的大人了
pretending to be a grown man in his 20s.
他没事的
He's fine.
但愿吧
I hope so.
你还能怎么样? 搬回去接着和他住吗?
What else can you do? Move back in with him?
不可能 我...我就是觉得这样不太好
No, of course not. I... I just feel bad.
我也这么觉得
Well, so do I,
但是你难道不想过和老婆住在一起
but don't you want to live with your wife
而且空调的温度
and set the thermostat
自己说了算的日子吗
to whatever you want
而且你想什么时候去洗手间
and have your body tell you
就什么时候去
when it's time to go to the bathroom,
而不用遵守每天早上
you know, not a schedule slipped
从门缝下面塞进来的时间表
underneath your door every morning?
其实我还挺喜欢时间表上的天气预报的
I did like that he had the weather on it.
你要相信 这样做是对的
Trust me, this is the right thing.
我知道
I know.
而且我们也不是抛弃了他
And it's not like we're abandoning him.
另外
Plus,
我们随时都可以跟他视频通话
we can FaceTime him whenever we want,
只要他那个世界里有人发明了苹果手机就好
you know, once iPhones are invented in his universe.
我简直不敢相信
I can't believe Sheldon
Sheldon居然让你做他的室友
asked you to be his roommate.
我不敢相信他居然去查我的信用记录
I can't believe he ran my credit.
嘿 你要是想找个人合租的话
Hey, if you're open to living with someone great,
我给你一千刀求你带走Stuart
I'll give you $1,000 to take Stuart.
在把这种生物领回家之前
You really should've gone on the Internet
真的应该上网好好查查
and checked how long that kind of thing lives
它能活多久
before you got one.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我只是觉得 你生命中可能有一个
I just thought you might have
需要面色苍白的怪咖来填补的空洞
a pasty, weirdo-shaped hole in your life.
我知道Sheldon有点怪
Hey, I know Sheldon's quirky,
可是他很聪明 又很有见地
but he's also brilliant and insightful.
我觉得把他叫做怪咖有点不合适吧
I think calling him a weirdo is a little unfair.
2003年的生活 我回来了!
Hello, 2003!
嗨 我们给你买了泰国菜
Hey, we brought you Thai.
家具都去哪了?
Where is everything?
对于现在的我来说 它们都在未来
In my present, it's in the future.
对于现在的你来说 我在建材城的停车场里
In your present, it's been crammed in the bedroom
找了个有上进心的年轻人
by an enterprising young man
帮我都搬进卧室堆着了
I met in The Home Depot parking lot.
我明白你在干什么
I know what you're doing.
你想引起我们的注意 让我们对你感到愧疚
You're trying to get attention so we'll feel bad for you,
不过这不可能
but it's not happening.
不 我只是想知道 所有人都离开我之后
No, what I'm doing is trying to figure out
我应该怎么一个人生活
how to live my life now that everyone is leaving me.
你真是够了 我们就住在走廊对面
Will you knock it off? We're across the hall.
就像现在年轻人常说的那样 "跟我的手说吧" (意为 我不听)
As the kids are saying today, "Talk to the hand."
他们可不这么说
They're not saying that.
2003年的时候他们会这么说的
They are in 2003.
不 真的不会
No, they're really not.
# 索尔和琼斯博士 #
# Thor and Dr. Jones #
#Thor and Dr. Jones #
# 一个离开了洛基 #
# One runs from Loki #
# 一个离开了圣石 #
# The other runs from stones. #
你觉得怎么样?
So, what do you think?
哇哦
Wow.
离开了圣石说的是...那个大石块
Runs from stones means that... that big boulder,
可是我找不到跟大石块押韵的词
but I couldn't rhyme anything with boulder.
(英文中都押韵)
湿冷 时间
Colder, shoulder,
士兵 文件...
soldier, folder...
好吧 好吧 你说的对
Right, yeah, right.
但是...
But...
你觉得怎么样嘛?
what do you think?
我觉得 挺可爱的
I think it's very cute.
可爱? 这不是可爱
Cute? It's not cute.
可爱说的是那些打扮成蔬菜的小孩
Cute is children dressed as vegetables.
好吧好吧 不是可爱
Okay, fine, it's not cute.
说实话 你根本就不喜欢对不对
Just be honest. You don't like it.
我可没这么说
I didn't say that.
我... 我只是更喜欢那种能跟着跳舞的音乐
I... I just like music you can dance to.
这个也可以跳舞啊！
You can dance to this!
呃 这样...
Um, uh, uh...
# 索尔和琼斯博士 #
# Thor and Dr. Jones #
# 一个玩闪电 #
# One plays with lightning #
# 一个玩骨头 #
# The other plays with bones. #
嘿 你听我说 这首歌有点问题
I'm telling you, dude, the song has no groove.
你没办法跟着它跳舞
You can't dance to it.
那又怎样?
Who cares?
我觉得"月球上的脚印"要做的音乐是
I thought the whole point of Footprints on the Moon
它能启发人们的思考
was to write songs that make people think.
可以一举两得啊
You can do both,
就像迈克尔·杰克逊的"Billie Jean"
like Michael Jackson's "Billie Jean."
你可以一边跳舞 一边思考
While you're dancing you're thinking, like,
"该死 这到底是哪个妹子?"
"Darn it, whose baby is it?"
你怎么会有这种想法?
Where's this coming from?
几个小时之前 我们都超爱这首歌的
A few hours ago, we both loved this song.
我现在也超爱它
I still love it.
我觉得还有提升空间
I just think there's room for improvement.
你弹给Emily听了 是不是?
You played it for Emily, didn't you?
- 是啊 那又怎样?  - 你太没主见了
- Yeah, so what?  - You are such a wimp.
她不喜欢 现在你也不喜欢了
She didn't like it, now you don't like it.
才不是 作为一个音乐家我需要进步
No, no. I'm just evolving as a musician.
你才是拘泥在过去的那个人
You're the one who's stuck in the past.
你说的过去就在中午!
The past was lunch!
你知不知道现在是什么情况?
You know what's really happening here?
你的女朋友在破坏我们的乐队
Your girlfriend is breaking up our band.
她和乐队没有关系
She has nothing to do with this.
我的想法我做主
I am my own man.
拜托 明明是谁愿意和你睡觉
Oh, please. Your brain belongs
你的脑子就是谁的
to whoever's willing to sleep with you.
- 这太扯了  - 是吗?
- That is so not true.  - Really?
还记得那次你要为Rachel Bernstein
Remember when you were gonna get circumcised
割包皮的事儿吗?
for Rachel Bernstein?
那事和Rachel没有关系
That had nothing to do with Rachel.
那事是裤拉链坏了导致的过激反应
It was an overreaction to a bad zipper injury.
我不想继续了
I don't need this.
我要退出乐队!
I'm quitting the band!
行啊 我也退出!
Fine, I quit, too!
那就滚出我家!
Then get out of my house!
乐意之极!
With pleasure!
Raj 等等
Raj, wait.
你怎么让我等了这么久?
What took you so long?
兄弟 我知道
Buddy, I know me
我搬去Penny家对你来说是个大变化
moving in with Penny feels like a big change,
但这并不是
but it's not.
你怎么可以这么说?
How can you say that?
Amy离开我了
Amy's gone,
你俩又结婚了
and you two are married now,
所以你俩要离开也只是时间问题
so it's only a matter of time before you're gone, too.
你根本不知道会发生什么
Okay, you don't know what's gonna happen.
不 我知道
No, I do.
以后你俩会想要更大的空间
Eventually you'll want more space,
接着就会搬进一座房子
and you'll move into a house,
接着本来是一周几次的聚餐
and then instead of dinner a couple of times a week,
变成了一月几次
it'll only be a couple of times a month,
最后又会变成
and then it'll only be
特殊时间才会相聚
on special occasions,
比如Bernadette和Wolowitz离婚的时候
like when Bernadette divorces Wolowitz.
或... 或者
Or... or... or like
在Koothrappali那个怪胎女朋友
when Koothrappali's weird girlfriend
指认出埋他的尸体的地方
admits where she buried his body.
或者 在Amy的婚礼上
Or Amy's wedding,
她要嫁给比我还好的人了
where she's marrying someone better than me.
好了 听着
Okay, look,
我们不会急着做出下一步行动
we don't need to rush into anything.
好吗?
All right?
除了Leonard搬去和我住
Maybe instead of Leonard moving in with me,
其它都保持原样
we just leave things the way they are,
而且...
and...
我们会在那边睡几天
sometimes we'll sleep over there,
然后在这边睡几天
and sometimes we'll sleep over here.
但是多数睡在这边
But mostly here.
好的
Sure.
那... 那你在餐厅里说的那些呢?
W... W... What about what you said in the restaurant?
不会一直这样下去的
Well, it's not forever.
暂时而已
It's just for a while.
你要是想的话 把他当成我们家的宠物狗好了
If you want, we can think of him like he's our dog.
可以 可以
You can.
你们回家了我会摇头晃尾
I'm happy when you come home.
而且我害怕烟花
And I'm scared of fireworks.
顺便说一句 七月四日我们都睡这边(美国独立日)
And by the way, on July Fourth, we're all sleeping here.
好吧
Fine.
好的 太好了!
All right, great!
给我一分钟
Just give me one minute,
然后我再开始准备室友协议
and I'll get started on a new Roommate Agreement.
好的
Yeah.
Pratt没给我回消息 没问题了
Nothing from Pratt. We're good.
# 印第的辫子断了 #
# Indy' whip snapped #
# 索尔的大锤不见 #
# Thor's hammer missed #
# 是复仇者#
# It was Avenger #
# 对抗着考古学家 #
# Versus archeologist #
# 印第坚守阵地 #
# Indy held his ground #
# 用帽子耍了个酷 #
# And straightened his fedora #
# 索尔说 "挺漂亮" #
# Thor said, "That's a nice look #
# 虽然我们在1944年啊 #
# In 1944-a" #
# 索尔和琼斯博士 #
# Thor and Dr. Jones #
# 一个会放电 #
# One plays with lightning #
# 一个玩骨头 #
# The other plays bones #
# 索尔和琼斯博士 #
# Thor and Dr. Jones #
# 一个会放电 #
# One plays with lightning #
# 一个会倒斗 #
# The other plays bones. #
能不能唱点我们可以跳舞的歌
Play something we can dance to.